Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Climbing Up against All Odds
Episode 47
I want to become stronger.
That way, I can protect everyone, just like Big Brother.
Oh no, oh no!
The Bottomless Abyss is erupting!
Everyone, take cover!
Hold on tight!
Quick, grab onto me!
It’s finally over.
We really owe it all to Brother Dahuang.
With Brother Dahuang guarding our village,
we don’t have to be afraid of anything anymore.
Brother Dahuang is the best.
That’s great—thanks to Brother Dahuang.
Little Brown, what’s wrong?
I want to guard the village with you, too.
But I’m not strong enough yet.
Then you need to train even harder
and become just as strong as me.
Then, you can guard the village and save the world alongside me.
Can I really do it?
You certainly can.
With your level of power…
It’s impossible.
Someone like you…
How could you possibly get out of there?
Open your eyes and look.
I am standing right in front of you.
This is…
…the best proof.
But you can’t even beat me.
Just because you can’t do it, why assume others can’t either?
You must be lying. You’re a liar.
Stop deluding yourself.
Someone like you, who wouldn’t even dare approach the edge of the Bottomless Abyss,
what right do you have to question me here?
He actually managed to climb up to this level.
Maybe we really can get out of here.
If it were that simple to climb up,
we wouldn’t have been trapped for so long.
Careful—there are no handholds or footholds in this area; you can’t climb it.
It’s a sheer vertical drop further up; it’s unclimbable.
Unclimbable?
Then I’ll just jump.
What are you doing?
I never thought that would work.
I didn’t either.
It was just now, while sliding down,
that I realized it when my foot accidentally touched a falling piece of paper.
As my body turned into lines, it became lighter, too.
It seems I’ve undergone some kind of change.
Oh no, the path ends here.
That was a close call.
We’ve been climbing for so long,
yet we still have so far to go; it’s as if we haven’t moved forward at all.
That is the most terrifying thing about the Bottomless Abyss.
No matter how hard you try to climb up…
the way out feels as distant as the horizon
It crushes your spirit, time and time again,
leaving you with a sense of helpless despair deep down
If everything could be accomplished easily,
life would be so boring, wouldn’t it?
Life is only interesting when it’s full of challenges
Everyone, look up!
More paper is drifting down
Hold on tight—we’re setting off again
I want to become stronger, so I can protect everyone just like you do
He reminds me of someone I used to know
Who could it be?
Little Brown is working out again.
It’s Big Brother.
The eruption has stopped.
Thank goodness, everyone is safe.
Oh no!
Brother Dahuang fell into the rift while trying to save us.
Big Brother, I’m coming to save you right now.
Big Brother!
Little Brown.
Big Brother, this time it’s my turn to save you.
Almost there.
Big Brother!
Quick, grab my hand!
Watch out!
Little Brown, grab hold of me!
Little Brown, do you remember the promise we made that day?
I remember. We were going to get stronger together…
protect the village together, and save the world together.
I can’t go back anymore.
But you can.
No…
Goodbye, Little Brown.
Big Brother…
Little Brown, you have to get stronger for my sake.
Protect the village for me.
The terror of the Abyss Bottomless
I know better than anyone…
Once you’re sucked in, there’s no getting out.
It seems your toughness is all talk.
Deep down, you’ve long been terrified of the Bottomless Abyss.
Nonsense.
You can’t withstand a single one of my blows…
so why do you keep getting back up?
Because I have companions to protect; I can’t fall.
Impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
Brother Dahuang, I will definitely carry on your legacy,
continue to protect the village, and keep getting stronger…
strong enough to save this world.
I have a way to help you protect your village
Why not join us?
For the sake of everything I protect, I must defeat you
I won’t give up
Little Brown
Hang in there, everyone
I promised to get everyone out, and I will
Not a single one left behind
I finally remember who I am
Now let us help you too, Sparky
Everyone, let’s help Sparky together!
Sparky!
Accept this power of ours!
Gotcha, Sparky!
So it was you guys.
Hang in there, Sparky!
Just one more step!
If I break through this layer, I can summon my Protagonist Aura!
I absolutely won’t let your kindness go to waste!
Protagonist Aura…
You’ve got to be kidding me.
Don’t tell me I don’t deserve the Protagonist Aura?
Goodbye, everyone.
Have I already faded away?
Why haven’t I fallen?
It’s my aura.
As expected, I still have the protagonist’s aura.
So, let’s charge out of this
Bottomless Abyss together.
Protagonist Aura!
Charge!
Charge, Sparky!
Lead us toward the light!
We made it out!
Little Brown. Stop it.
That voice…could it be…
Big Brother?
I never imagined you’d become this strong.
You…
are actually still alive.
Thanks to Sparky.
He was the one who saved us from the Bottomless Abyss.
But…with so little power, how could he…
We had already given up hope.
Quietly waiting to fade away.
It was his refusal to give up that let us see hope again.
Why? How does he possess such indomitable strength?
Little Brown, he achieved what none of us could.
He pulled it off
He holds infinite possibilities
Maybe he can help us save this world
Go in and save him
Brown
Will you come with me?
To be continued